

Cindy Gnaedinger DEVELOPER | TRANSLATOR

(54)3516544771 cyn.gnaedinger@gmail.com Córdoba, Argentina <u>LinkedIn</u> <u>GitHub</u> <u>Skype</u>

ABOUT ME

English - Spanish Translator with 2+ years training in web development. Passionate about communication and the creation of interactive, user-friendly virtual interfaces. I am actively pursuing to engage in challenging projects, and to collaborate in an inspiring work environment. I am persistent, organized, collaborative, self-taught, and resourceful.

EDUCATION | COURSES

Fundación Pescar/EducaciónIT/L'Oréal/Accenture Full Stack Web Development

JavaScript, HTML, CSS, MongoDB, React, Node.js, OOP, SCRUM, emotional management, assertive communication, teamwork, public speaking, resilience, self-management, initiative, critical and logical thinking 07/2023 - 01/2024

Coursera

Google Data Analytics

Spreadsheets, Excel, SQL, R, data analysis, data cleaning, data visualization, data-driven decision-making - 09/2023 - 11/2023

Alura/Oracle

Frontend Web Development

JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Java, SQL 08/2022 - 01/2023

Universidad Adventista del Plata

Sworn English Spanish Translation 03/2011 - 12/2016

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Developer Trainee

Atila Software

03/2024 - 06/2024

VB.Net, JavaScript, SQL, Flutter, HTML, CSS, JQuery

EN > SP Translator/Editor

Freelance/Remote

03/2020 - 07/2023

Translation of texts related to the IT field from English into Spanish, creation of linguistic content for Spanish Al training

DEV PROJECTS

Sabor Solidario

Group project

09/2023 - 02/2024

JavaScript, HTML, CSS, MongoDB, Node.js, React Web page in which we aim to address the issue of food scarcity by connecting food donors with community dining facilities

Responsive Personal Portfolio

2023

JavaScript, HTML, CSS

Responsive design, dark-light mode, smooth scroll

SKILLS | TOOLS

- Trados SDL
- memoQ
- HTML advanced
- · CSS advanced
- Figma advanced
- Excel advanced
- · Spreadsheets advanced
- JavaScript intermediate
- MongoDB intermediate
- · Node.js intermediate
- SQL intermediate
- Git GitHub intermediate
- VB .Net initial
- Java initial